Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- C, 298311
  - Cooperative League of the U.S.A.: Bureau of Cooperative Medicine, 1937; 324127 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Productive Federation (England), 1904; 299386 (Box 30)
  - Cooperative Project (New York, NY), undated; 299387 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Publishing Society of Foreign Workers in the USSR I, 1931-1932; 327567 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Publishing Society of Foreign Workers in the USSR II, 1931-1932; 327568 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Publishing Society of Foreign Workers in the USSR I, 1933-1937; 299388 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Publishing Society of Foreign Workers in the USSR II, 1933-1937; 327569 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Reference Library (Dublin, Ireland), undated; 299389 (Box 30)
  - Cooperative Union (Chicago, IL), undated; 299391 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Union, Ltd. (England) I, 1896-1950s; 299390 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Union, Ltd. (England) II, 1896-1950s; 324128 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Union, Ltd. (England) III, 1896-1950s; 324129 (Box 30)
  - Co-operative Wholesale Society (Manchester, England), 1901-; 299392 (Box 30)
  - Co-ordinating Committee on Transit (New York, NY), undated; 299416 (Box 30)
  - Co-Partnership Tenants Housing Council (London), 1907; 299417 (Box 30)
  - Cornell Organization for Labor Action, 1980; 299418 (Box 30)
  - Corona, E. Elmhurst, Jackson Heights Peace Committee, 1968-1969, undated; 371954 (Box 30)
  - Corporate Campaign, undated; 299419 (Box 30)
  - Corporate Data Exchange, Inc., 1981-; 299420 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence Publishing Co. (Detroit, MI), 1954; 299421 (Box 31)
  - Contra Costa Citizens Against the War in Viet Nam, undated; 374357 (Box 31)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1917-; 299422 (Box 31)
  - Council Against Intolerance in America, 1940; 324167 (Box 31)
  - Council for a Livable World (Washington, DC), 1965-; 299423 (Box 31)
  - Council for Cooperative Development, 1944; 324168 (Box 31)
  - Council for Correspondence (New York, NY), 1961-1961; 299424 (Box 31)
  - Council for Democracy (New York, NY), 1942; 299425 (Box 31)
  - Council for Equal Job Opportunity, 1948; 412284 (Box 31)
  - Council for Pan American Democracy, 1941-1944; 299426 (Box 31)
  - Council for Social Action, undated; 299429 (Box 31)
  - Council for the Advancement of the Americas (New York, NY), undated; 299427 (Box 31)
  - Council for the Liberation of Daily Life, 1968; 324169 (Box 31)
  - Council of Economic Priorities, 1969-; 299428 (Box 31)
  - Council of Federated Organizations (U.S.) (civil rights), 1963-1965; 299430 (Box 31)
  - Council of Jewish Organizations, 2007-; 299431 (Box 31)
  - Council of Jewish Socialist Youth (U.S.), undated; 299432 (Box 31)
  - Council of Workers, Soldiers and Sailor of Toledo, Ohio, circa 1920; 324170 (Box 31)
  - Council on African Affairs (New York, NY), 1944-1950; 299433 (Box 31)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1912; 324171 (Box 31)
  - Council on Religion and International Affairs, 1966; 299434 (Box 31)
  - Counterattack (New York, NY) (anti-communism), 1948; 299435 (Box 31)
  - Cousins Coordinating Committee, undated; 324172 (Box 31)
  - CrimethInc., undated; 299436 (Box 31)
  - Critica Sociale, 1959; 299437 (Box 31)
  - Critical Art Ensemble, 2000-; 299438 (Box 31)
  - Critical Mass, 2000-; 299439 (Box 31)
  - Critical Resistance, 1997-; 299440 (Box 31)
  - Crosscurrents Press I, 1959-1962; 299441 (Box 31)
  - Crosscurrents Press II, 1959-1962; 324173 (Box 31)
  - Cuba Information Project (New York, NY), 1992-; 300062 (Box 31)
  - Cuba Policy Foundation (Washington, DC), 2000-; 299442 (Box 31)
  - Cuba Solidarity New York, 2002; 372946 (Box 31)
  - Cuban-American Civil Rights Committee, 1962; 300039 (Box 31)
  - Cuban Front: New York Delegation (New York, NY), undated; 300038 (Box 31)
  - Cure (Chicago, IL), 1963; 299443 (Box 31)
  - CUNY for all Coalition (New York, NY) (City University of New York), circa 2002; 299444 (Box 31)
  - Cyclohm, undated; 423149 (Box 31)
  - Czech-Slav Social Democratic Labour Party, 1910; 299445 (Box 31)
  - Czechoslovak-American Defense Committee, 1938; 299446 (Box 31)
  - Czechoslovak National Council of America, 1943; 324174 (Box 31)
  - Czechoslovak Social Democratic Labour Party, 1923-1930; 299447 (Box 31)
- D, 299448
  - Daily Press (St. Louis, MO), 1865; 299449 (Box 31)
  - Daniel DeLeon League (New York, NY), 1968-1969, undated; 299450 (Box 31)
  - Dan Wyman Books (Woodbury, CT): Catalog, 1985; 299451 (Box 31)
  - Dandelion (St. Paul, MN), 1978-1980; 299452 (Box 31)
  - Danville Collective (Danville, IL), 1971; 299453 (Box 31)
  - Database of American Labor Graphics (Berkeley, CA), undated; 299454 (Box 31)
  - Data Center (Oakland, CA), undated; 299455 (Box 31)
  - Davis-Putter Scholarship Fund (financial assistance to activists in pursuit of higher education), 1996; 299456 (Box 31)
  - Day Care Action Coaltion, undated; 324175 (Box 31)
  - D.C. Anti-Capitalist Convergence, 2002, undated; 372947 (Box 31)
  - D.C. Anti-Fascist Network, undated; 372948 (Box 31)
  - D.C. Anti-War Network, undated; 372949 (Box 31)
  - D.C. Nine Defense Committee (Dow Chemical), 1970; 324176 (Box 31)
  - D.C. Student Committee on the Transportation Crisis (DCSCTC), undated; 374270 (Box 31)
  - D.C. Women's Liberation, undated; 379956 (Box 31)
  - De Leonist Society, 1988; 327573 (Box 31)
  - Debs Amnesty Committee (Chicago, IL), undated; 299457 (Box 31)
  - Debs Centennial Committee (New York, NY), 1955; 299458 (Box 31)
  - Debs Labor School (New York, NY), 1938; 299459 (Box 31)
  - Debs Memorial Radio Fund (New York, NY), undated; 299460 (Box 31)
  - Debs School of Social Science (Philadelphia, PA), 1935-1937; 299461 (Box 31)
  - December 4th Movement (New York, NY) (Black Panthers), 1970; 299463 (Box 31)
  - December 15 Indochina Solidarity Coalition, 1973; 374220 (Box 31)
  - Declaration of Conscience Against the War in Vietnam, undated; 373803 (Box 31)
  - Deep Dish Network, circa 1997; 324177 (Box 31)
  - Defend Education, 2010-; 324178 (Box 31)
  - Defenders of 3 Against HUAC (Washington, DC), undated; 299462 (Box 31)
  - Defensa Institucional Cubana, 1962; 299464 (Box 31)
  - Defense Committee (Norfolk, VA), 1970s; 299465 (Box 31)
  - Defense Committee for the Prisoners of Texas, undated; 379957 (Box 31)
  - Democracy March, undated; 372950 (Box 31)
  - Democracy Now!, undated; 324179 (Box 31)
  - Democracy Project, undated; 324180 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Agenda (New York, NY), 1980s; 299466 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Congressional Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1906; 377471 (Box 116)
  - Democratic Congressional Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1910; 377472 (Box 116)
  - Democratic Left Book Review, 1974-1975; 324181 (Box 31)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1932-1960, undated; 324182 (Box 31)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1896; 377473 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1900; 377474 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1902; 377475 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1904; 377476 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1908; 377477 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1912; 377478 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1916; 377479 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1928; 377480 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1932; 377481 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1940; 377482 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1952; 377483 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1956; 377484 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Convention (New York, NY): Non Delegates Handbook, undated; 324183 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Party of Vietnam (cards), undated; 325715 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Federation (U.S.), 1957; 299467 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Federation: Greater Miami Branch, 1964; 299468 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (U.S.) I, 1970-1980; 299469 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (U.S.) II, 1970-1980; 299470 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (U.S.) III, 1970-1980; 324184 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (U.S.) IV, 1970-1980, undated; 324185 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialists at NYU, 1998-; 324186 (Box 32)
  - Democratic Socialists of America I, 1980s-; 299472 (Box 32)
  - Democratic Socialists of America II, 1980s-; 324187 (Box 32)
  - Democratic Socialists of America III, 1980s-; 324188 (Box 32)
  - Democratic Socialists of America: Youth Sector, 1980s; 299474 (Box 32)
  - Democratic Student Association, 372951 (Box 32)
  - Demokratia (New York, NY), 1974, undated; 299475 (Box 32)
  - Denver Chicano Liberation Defense Committee, 1973; 299478 (Box 32)
  - Descendants of the American Revolution, 1940, undated; 324189 (Box 32)
  - Desis Rising Up and Moving (DRUM), 2001-2004, undated; 299479 (Box 32)
  - Detroit Coalition to End the War Now, undated; 375399 (Box 32)
  - Detroit Committee to Keep America out of the War (Vietnam), undated; 299480 (Box 32)
  - Detroit Free Press, 1970; 374746 (Box 32)
  - Detroit Labor College, 1933; 299481 (Box 32)
  - Detroit Labor Committee for Peace and Justice, undated; 299482 (Box 32)
  - Detroit Working Peoples Association, 2005; 372953 (Box 32)
  - Deutsche-Anarcho Syndikalisten, 1936; 299483 (Box 32)
  - Deutschen Sozialdemokratischen Arbeiterpartei in Der Tschechoslowakischen Republik, 1922-1923; 299484 (Box 32)
  - Deutscher Freihiets-Bund (New York, NY), 1935; 299476 (Box 32)
  - Develop Don't Destroy (Brooklyn, NY), 2004; 324190 (Box 32)
  - Development Education Centre (Toronto, Canada), 1973-1975; 299477 (Box 32)
  - Dial Publishing Company (New York, NY), undated; 299486 (Box 32)
  - Diggers Communications Company, circa 1967; 299487 (Box 32)
  - Dill Pickle Press (Muscatine, IA), circa 1970s; 299488 (Box 32)
  - Direct Action for Justice in Palestine, 2002-; 299489 (Box 32)
  - Direct Action Network, 1999-; 299490 (Box 32)
  - Direct Action Network (Chicago), 2002; 299491 (Box 32)
  - Direct Action Network (New York, NY), 2002; 299492 (Box 32)
  - Disarm Education Fund, undated; 299493 (Box 32)
  - Dispossessed Network, 2000-; 299494 (Box 32)
  - Dissent (New York, NY) (serial), 1961-; 299495 (Box 32)
  - Distributive Worker, 1971; 374132 (Box 32)
  - Dollars and Sense (Somerville, MA), undated; 299496 (Box 32)
  - Draft Law Group (Yale Law School), 1968; 373856 (Box 32)
  - Draft Resistance Committee (Detroit, MI), undated; 299497 (Box 32)
  - Draft Resisters Union Movement, 1967; 373953 (Box 32)
  - Dramatic Society (New York, NY), 1937; 338459 (Box 32)
  - Drop the I-Word Campaign, 387525 (Box 32)
  - Drop the Rock (Rockefeller Drug Laws), 2001-; 299498 (Box 32)
  - Drunken Boat (New York, NY), 1994-; 299499 (Box 32)
  - Du Quoin Miners Defense Committee, 1939; 323271 (Box 32)
  - Dubois Theater Guild, undated; 299500 (Box 32)
  - Duke Progressive Alliance (Duke University), 2002-2003; 324191 (Box 32)
  - DYKE Action Machine (DAM!), 2002-; 299501 (Box 32)
  - Dykes Against Racism Everywhere, 1989-; 299502 (Box 32)
  - Dykes for an American Revolution (poetry), 1966-, undated; 324192 (Box 32)
- E, 299485
  - Earth First!, 2004; 299504 (Box 32)
  - Earth Liberation Front, undated; 299503 (Box 32)
  - Earth Matters!, 2002-; 299505 (Box 32)
  - East and West Association (U.S.), 1942; 299506 (Box 32)
  - East Bay Civil Rights Congress, undated; 327574 (Box 32)
  - East Bay Women's Liberation, 1969; 379958 (Box 32)
  - East Coast Conference of Socialist Sociologists, 1974-1976; 299507 (Box 32)
  - East Coast Conspiracy to Save Lives, 1970; 299508 (Box 32)
  - EastRev, undated; 422943 (Box 32)
  - East Side Federation of Italians to Defend America, undated; 324193 (Box 32)
  - East Side Service Organization, 1967-1968; 299509 (Box 32)
  - East Side Tenants Moratorium Committee, undated; 374768 (Box 32)
  - East Timor Action Network, 2011, undated; 372954 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperative League (Brooklyn, NY) I, 1938-1948; 299511 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperative League (Brooklyn, NY) II, 1938-1948; 324194 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperative Wholesale I, 1941-1942; 299512 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperative Wholesale II, 1940-1943; 324195 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperatives (New York, NY), 1947; 299510 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Marxist Scholars' Conference (New York, NY), 1980; 299513 (Box 32)
  - Eastern New England Conference for Equal Opportunities, 1940-1944; 299514 (Box 32)
  - Eastern States' Socialist Conference, undated; 299515 (Box 32)
  - Ecology Action East (New York, NY), 1969-1970; 299516 (Box 32)
  - Ecology Action Educational Institute (Berkeley, CA), 1960s; 299517 (Box 32)
  - Economists Against the Arms Race (New York, NY), undated; 300826 (Box 32)
  - Ediciones Espanolas, 1936-1938; 299518 (Box 32)
  - Editions Servier le Peuple (Corona, Elmhurst, NY), 1983; 299519 (Box 32)
  - Editorial Argonauta (Buenos Aires), 1920-1921; 299520 (Box 32)
  - Education Exploration Center, 1980; 546998 (Box 32)
  - Educational and Cultural Fund of the Electrical Industry, 1991; 324196 (Box 32)
  - Educational Policies Commission, 1944; 299521 (Box 32)
  - Eighth CD for Impeachment (Jerrold Nadler, New York), 2008-; 324197 (Box 33)
  - El Comite-M.I.N.P., undated; 327577 (Box 33)
  - El Grupo Escindido, 2012; 452610 (Box 33)
  - El Rescate Human Rights Department "Report of the Salvadora Trade Union Movement", 1985; 299522 (Box 33)
  - Electoral Reform Society, 1913; 299523 (Box 33)
  - Elmira Unemployment Council, 1935; 532105 (Box 33)
  - Embassies of Reconciliation (London), 1937; 299524 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee I, 1954-1964, undated; 299525 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee II, 1955-1964, undated; 324198 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Coalition Against Martial Law, circa 1990s; 324199 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee for a National Mobilization Against Racism, 1974; 299526 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee for Peace in the Middle East and Vietnam, undated; 299527 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Scholars, 1937-1941; 299528 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists, undated; 299529 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee on Rent and Housing, Inc. (New York, NY), undated; 324200 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee on United States Policy in Nicaragua, undated; 299530 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee to Defend Democracy in Chili (San Jose, CA), undated; 372955 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Conference Committee (U.S.), 1970, undated; 299531 (Box 33)
  - Emergency National Council Against U.S. Intervention in Central America and the Caribbean, 1986; 299532 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Peace Campaign (U.S.), 1936; 299533 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Peace Mobilization Committee of Greater New York, 1940; 299534 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Project for Saigon Civilian Prisoners, 1970; 374338 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Public Integration Committee, undated; 335578 (Box 33)
  - Emma Lazarus Federation of Jewish Women's Clubs, 1981-1983; 299535 (Box 33)
  - Emmaus House (New York, NY), undated; 299536 (Box 33)
  - Empire State College: Center for Labor Studies, 1974-1977; 299537 (Box 33)
  - Empire State College: Faculty Action Committee, 1977; 299538 (Box 33)
  - Empire State College: Harry Van Arsdale Jr. School of Labor Studies, 1985-; 299539 (Box 33)
  - Employees for Improved Mass Transit, undated; 412274 (Box 33)
  - Employed and Unemployed Citizens of Colorado, undated; 437214 (Box 33)
  - Employers' Association of Boston, 1904; 299540 (Box 33)
  - Employment Research Associates, 1980s; 299541 (Box 33)
  - End Poverty League, 1934; 299542 (Box 33)
  - End the Draft Committee, 1963-1965; 299543 (Box 33)
  - End the Draft in '63, 1963; 299544 (Box 33)
  - English Land Restoration League, undated; 299545 (Box 33)
  - English Peoples Convention, 1941; 324201 (Box 33)
  - Enraged Ones, circa 1972; 299546 (Box 33)
  - Environment Group, Inc., 1970-1976; 299547 (Box 33)
  - Environmental Action Coalition, 1970; 299548 (Box 33)
  - Environmental Action Foundation (Washington, DC), undated; 305252 (Box 33)
  - Environmental Project on Central America, 1989; 412397 (Box 33)
  - Environmentalists for Full Employment (Washington, DC), 1985; 299549 (Box 33)
  - Equal Income Party, 1934; 372956 (Box 33)
  - Equality League (New York, NY), undated; 325716 (Box 33)
  - Ethical Anarchism (Tucson, AZ), undated; 305845 (Box 33)
  - Ethical Culture School/ Fieldston School (New York, NY), 1934; 299550 (Box 33)
  - Ethical Humanist Society, undated; 373804 (Box 33)
  - Ethiopian Revolution Information Center, 1977; 372957 (Box 33)
  - Ethiopian Students Union in North America, 1971-1976; 299551 (Box 33)
  - Etudier L'Anarchisme, 1999; 299552 (Box 33)
  - Eugene Debs School (New York, NY), undated; 299553 (Box 33)
  - Eugene V. Debs Foundation I, 1995-; 299554 (Box 33)
  - Eugene V. Debs Foundation II, 1995-; 324202 (Box 33)
  - Eugene Dennis Defense Committee, undated; 437213 (Box 33)
  - Evangelicals for Social Action, 1983; 299555 (Box 33)
  - Every Mother is a Working Mother Network, 2002, undated; 372958 (Box 33)
  - Everyday Apocalypse, undated; 324203 (Box 33)
  - Ex-Service Movement for Peace (Great Britain), 1951-1953; 299556 (Box 33)
  - External Tendency of the 1st, 1983; 327578 (Box 33)
  - Eye Opener, undated; 299557 (Box 33)
- F, 299558
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain), 1913-2000; 299559 (Box 33)
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain): Pamphlets, 1900; 324204 (Box 33)
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain): Pamphlets I, 1906-1990; 299560 (Box 33)
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain): Pamphlets II, 1906-1990; 299561 (Box 33)
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain): Pamphlets III, 1906-1990; 299562 (Box 33)
  - Facing Reality Publishing Committee, 1964; 299563 (Box 33)
  - Facing Reality Publications, Friends Of (Detroit, MI), 1970; 299564 (Box 33)
  - Fact: A Monograph a Month (London), 1937; 299565 (Box 33)
  - Faculty Action, undated; 327584 (Box 33)
  - Faculty of Social Science (New York, NY), 1958; 299566 (Box 33)
  - Fair Play for Cuba Committee, 1961-1963; 299567 (Box 34)
  - Fair Play for Cuba Committee: Pamphlets, 1961-1964; 299568 (Box 34)
  - Fair Share for Working Families, undated; 299569 (Box 34)
  - Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting, 2000, undated; 299570 (Box 34)
  - Falling Wall Press, 1971-1975; 299571 (Box 34)
  - Families of Resisters of Amnesty, 1973; 299572 (Box 34)
  - Families of the Baltimore Smith Act Victims, 1951; 372961 (Box 34)
  - Families United for Racial and Economic Equality (FUREE) (Brooklyn, NY), undated; 299574 (Box 34)
  - Family and Friends of Daniel McGowan, undated; 372962 (Box 34)
  - Family Trust (New York, NY), 1970; 299573 (Box 34)
  - Fannie Lou Hamer Project, 2000-2001, undated; 372963 (Box 34)
  - Far East Reporter, 1959; 372964 (Box 34)
  - Far East Spotlight, undated; 299575 (Box 34)
  - Farm Credit Administration, 1937-1959; 324211 (Box 34)
  - Farm Labor Organizing Committee, 1983-1986; 327585 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Association of Minnesota, 1925, 1936; 299576 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party, 1920-1924; 299577 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party, 1932-1936; 299578 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party (Cook County, IL), undated; 299579 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party of Wayne County (MI), undated; 299580 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party (New Hampshire), undated; 299581 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party (New York), 1929; 299582 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party (Washington), 1923; 299583 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Political Federation, undated; 299584 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Progressive Federation, 1920-1935; 299585 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Reconstruction League of Oklahoma, circa 1920s; 299586 (Box 34)
  - Farmers National Committee for Action, undated; 327586 (Box 34)
  - Farmers' Union Co-operative Hospital Association, undated; 299587 (Box 34)
  - Farmworker Justice Fund (Washington, DC), 2001-; 299588 (Box 34)
  - Federacion Anarquista Internacional (Chile), 1960; 299589 (Box 34)
  - Federacion Iberica de Juventudes Libertarias, undated; 299590 (Box 34)
  - Federacion Obrera Regional Argentina, 1961; 299591 (Box 34)
  - Federacion Universitan a Socialista Puertorriquena, 1974; 299592 (Box 34)
  - Federal Art Project, 1934-1938; 299593 (Box 34)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America I, 1918-1946, undated; 299594 (Box 34)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America II, 1918-1946, undated; 299595 (Box 34)
  - Federal Emergency Relief Administration: Workers Education, 1934-1935; 324212 (Box 34)
  - Federal Ministry for Expellees, Refugees, and War Victims, 1959; 379959 (Box 34)
  - Federated Americans Against Israeli Racism (FAIR), undated; 327587 (Box 34)
  - Federated Associations for Impartial Review (Civilian Review Board), undated; 372965 (Box 34)
  - Federated Farmer-Labor Party (U.S.), undated; 299597 (Box 34)
  - Federated Industries of Washington, 1924-1925; 299598 (Box 34)
  - Federated Labor Schools of Western Pennsylvania (flier), undated; 324218 (Box 34)
  - Federated Press: Eastern Bureau, 1943-; 299599 (Box 34)
  - Federation for Industrial Retention and Renewal (FIRR), 1992-1994; 324213 (Box 34)
  - Federation for Progress, 1984; 299600 (Box 34)
  - Federation for Support of Jewish Philanthropic Societies, 1920; 324214 (Box 34)
  - Federation of Consumers (New York, NY), 1917; 324215 (Box 34)
  - Federation of Labour Conference, 1959; 299601 (Box 34)
  - Federation of Residential Settlements (Great Britain), 1922; 335702 (Box 34)
  - Federation of the Russian Anarchist-Communist Group of U.S.A. and Canada, 1934; 299596 (Box 34)
  - Federation of Unemployed Workers' League of America, undated; 299602 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship Farm Co-Operative Association (Stelton, NJ), 1912; 299603 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship House, 1913-1917; 324216 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.) I, 1970-; 299604 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.) II, 1970-; 299605 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.) III, 1970-; 299606 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.) IV, 1970-; 324217 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.): Local Volunteers Program, Aids for Peace Action, 1957-; 299607 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Socialist Christians, 1938; 299608 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Southern Churchmen, 1946; 299609 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Youth for Peace, undated; 299610 (Box 34)
  - Female Labor Reform Association, 1982; 327594 (Box 35)
  - Female Liberation/Cell 16 (Boston, MA), 1969-1970; 299611 (Box 35)
  - Female Liberation of Nashville, TN, 1969; 299612 (Box 35)
  - Feminist Center for Human Growth and Development, Inc., undated; 379960 (Box 35)
  - Feminist Majority Foundation, undated; 372966 (Box 35)
  - Feminist Organization for Communication, Action and Service, 1968; 299613 (Box 35)
  - Feminist Press, 1972-1985; 299614 (Box 35)
  - Feminist Union of New Haven (Connecticut), undated; 299615 (Box 35)
  - Feminists (New York, NY), 1969; 299616 (Box 35)
  - Feminists of Children's Media, 1971-1972; 299617 (Box 35)
  - Fernwood Press (Toronto, Canada), 2001-; 299618 (Box 35)
  - Festival Del Pueblo (Boston, MA), undated; 299619 (Box 35)
  - Fierce! (Fabulous Independent Educated for Community Empowerment), 2002-; 299620 (Box 35)
  - Fifteenth Street Manifesto Group, 2008; 412372 (Box 35)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee, 1965-1968; 299621 (Box 35)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee, 1969-1970; 299622 (Box 35)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee, 1971-1975; 299623 (Box 35)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee I, undated; 299624 (Box 35)